bach-cantatas.com 2019-12-09

# Bach Cantatas Website - Privacy-Policy

****

**Bach Cantatas Website - Privacy Policy**  
  
---  
****

**Introduction**  
  
The Operators of the Bach Cantatas Website (in this Policy: " **us** ", " **we** " and " **our** ") respects your privacy. This Policy (the “ **Policy** ”) explains our privacy practices for our Services at [www.bach-cantatas.com](http://www.bach-cantatas.com/) and any other related domain names (collectively - the " **Service** " or the “ **Services** ”). It describes the ways your personal information and data is collected and used and the rights and options available to you with respect to your information. 

This Policy is incorporated to the Service's Terms of Use (the “ **Terms** ”) and constitutes an integral part of them.  
  
****

**Information that we may process**  
  
We may process the following types of information -  
  
(1) Device and traffic information - information identifying and relating to your computer and mobile device and communication and transmission data that your computer and mobile device generates when you use the Services; 

(2) Personal details - Information that you provide us when you register to the Services, or any part thereof, or when you communicate with us or other users of the Service.  
  
The following sections of this Policy provide additional details on each type of information that we may collect and what we might do with that information.  
  
****

**Device and traffic information**  
  
We may collect data related to your use of the Service, such as information about the frequency of your use of the Service and content that you viewed, downloaded or otherwise used when using the Service. We may collect communication and transmission data that your computer and mobile device generates or stores to help us provide the Service. For example, we may collect and receive the operating system version and IP address you use once you register to the Service.  
  
****

**Personal information that you provide us**  
  
The Website serves all Internet users. However, some Services, such as the Website’s discussion groups, are available to registered users only. When you register with the Service we may ask you to provide us with certain contact and personal details, such as your name and an active e-mail address and to enter a username and password. We may collect additional information, as required, when we exchange communications with you.

Please bear in mind that false, incorrect, or outdated, abusive or unlawful information may prevent you from registering and may impair our ability to provide you the full scope of the Service, or to contact you. 

When you register with the Service, you may be required to provide a username and set a unique password that will identify you each time you enter the Service. We may require other or additional means or methods of identification, from time to time. You agree to maintain your username and password in absolute confidentiality and refrain from disclosing them to others. Make sure that you change your password frequently and at least once every six months.  
  
****

**The ways we may use your personally identifiable information**  
  
We may use personally identifiable information for the following purposes -  
  
  * To provide you with the Service, its features and functionalities.
  * To send you notices and updates, to conduct surveys related to the Service and to provide you with information related to the Service – through the Service interface or through e-mail, as available.
  * To respond to messages that you send us, and to allow us to provide support and assistance.
  * To improve and customize your and other users' experience with the Service.
  * To enhance existing features of the Service and to develop new features and services. 
  * To prevent fraud, misappropriation, infringements, identity thefts and any other misuse of the Service.
  * To facilitate our internal managerial, archival, administrative and audit activities. 
  * To contact you as and when we believe it to be necessary.
  * To enforce the Terms and this Policy and prevent misuse of the Service; 
  * To comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies or competent authorities under any applicable law, when we have a good faith belief that our cooperation with such entities is legally mandated or meets the applicable legal standards.
  * To prevent imminent physical harm or damage to property.
  * To take any action in any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and us, or between you and other users or third parties with respect to, or in relation with the Service.

****

**Sharing information with others**  
  
We may share personally identifiable information with others in any of the following instances, or subject to your prior explicit consent:  
  
  * To operate, maintain and enhance the Service.
  * If you have breached the Terms, abused your rights to use the Service, or violated any applicable law. Your information may be shared with competent authorities and with any third party, as may be required.
  * If we reasonably believe that we are required by law to share or disclose your information.
  * In any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind involving you with respect to the Service. 
  * If the operation of the Service is organized within a different framework, or through another legal structure or entity, provided that those entities agree to be bound by the provisions of this Policy, with reasonably necessary changes taken into consideration; and

In any case other than the above, your personally identifiable information will be shared with others only if you provide us with your explicit prior consent.  
  
****

**Transfer of data outside your territory**  
  
The Service, by its nature as an online service, may store and process information and content (including through Cloud Services) in Europe, the United States and in other various locations throughout the globe. If you are a resident in a jurisdiction where transfer of your personal information to another jurisdiction requires your consent, then you provide us with your express and unambiguous consent to such transfer.  
  
****

**We use de-identified or aggregated information**  
  
We may use de-identified, statistical or aggregated information, including information that we process according to this policy, to properly operate the Service, to develop and improve the quality and functionality of the Service, to enhance your experience, to create new services, including customized services, to change or cancel existing features and for other research, development and statistical purposes. We may share, publish, post, disseminate, transmit or otherwise communicate or make available such information to suppliers, business partners, sponsors, developers, affiliates and any other third party, at our sole discretion, provided however, that we will not knowingly, or intentionally share information that can be reasonably used to reveal your identity without your consent.  
  
****

**Access to your personal information**  
  
You have a right to access your personally identifiable information if, and to the extent, we keep such data about you, and to update, rectify or remove such data. To apply for a copy of your information, please contact us at: [oron-a@inter.net.il](mailto:oron-a@inter.net.il)

Before allowing you to exercise your right, we will need to verify your identity. We will make the information available to you, subject to any legitimate constraints and pursuant to the applicable law. We may refuse your request, for example, if we are unable to identify you, or if we believe that removal of certain information may jeopardize activities or features of the Service, harm other users, or compromise our legal rights.   
  
****

**Securing your personal information**  
  
We and third parties on our behalf implement security measures to secure the information we store and process. While such security measures reduce the risk of security breaches, they do not provide absolute security. Therefore, while we take reasonable measures to secure the information, we cannot guarantee that it will be immune from any wrongdoings, malfunctions, unlawful interceptions or unauthorized access.   
  
****

**Changes to this Policy**  
  
From time to time, we may change and update the terms of this Policy. Technical changes in the S, new features and evolvement of relevant legal aspects, will require us to adapt this Policy. 

We will notify you, either through the Service, or through any other means, in our discretion, of any substantial change that we make to this Policy. The changes will apply to you seven (7) days following transmission of the display of the notice to you. You agree to be bound by all changes made in the terms of this Policy. Continuing to use the Service after that date will indicate your acceptance to the amended policy. If you do not agree with any of the amended terms, you must avoid any further use of the Service. 

We may also amend this Policy to comply with any legal requirements. In these cases, the amendments will become effective as required or ordered and we will send you a notice of such change.   
  
****

**Contact us**  
  
We are doing our utmost to comply with this Policy. If you have any questions, concerns or complaints regarding this policy, please refer them to: [oron-a@inter.net.il](mailto:oron-a@inter.net.il). After receiving your request, we may contact you to better understand your concerns and will make all efforts to promptly answer your question, or resolve your complaint.  
  
****

**Incorporated documents**  
  
The following documents, forms and policies are incorporated by reference to Privacy Policy and are part of the Terms. Whenever expressing your consent to the Policy you also acknowledge your consent to these documents, as well:  
Terms of Use  
Copyright Policy  
  
****

**Last updated:** April 29, 2015
